Guide to the Benjamin Sussman Papers, 1940-1995
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- E: Design, (2 boxes)
  - E-1103: Caricature (Box 13)
  - E-1104: Sculpture (Box 13)
  - E-1105: Still life (Box 13)
  - E-1106: Plant life (Box 13)
  - E-1107: Landscape (Box 13)
  - E-1108: Seascape (Box 13)
- F: Merchandising/Sales Promotion, (2 boxes)
  - F-100: Merchandising, general, including communications (Box 13)
  - F-101: Merchandising effectiveness (Box 13)
  - F-102: Associations (Box 13)
  - F-103: Production almanacs (Box 13)
  - F-200: Media merchandising support, general (Box 13)
  - F-201: Reprints, preprints (Box 13)
  - F-300: Dealer promotions, general (Box 13)
  - F-400: Tie-ins, general (Box 13)
  - F-401: Advertising tie-ins (Box 13)
  - F-500: Retail promos, general (Box 13)
  - F-501: Grand openings (Box 13)
  - F-502: Special events, general (Box 13)
  - F-503: Dealer follow-thru (Box 13)
  - May 1968 contest, general (Box 13)
  - F-600: Contests, general (Box 13)
  - F-601: Entry blanks, rules (Box 13)
  - F-603: Consumer contests (Box 13)
  - F-604: Dealer incentives (Box 13)
  - F-605: Sales incentives (Box 13)
  - F-606: Follow-up (Box 13)
  - F-700: Consumer incentives (Box 13)
  - F-701: Couponing (Box 13)
  - F-702: Product sampling (Box 13)
  - F-800: Exhibits, shows, general (Box 13)
  - F-801: Trade show audits (Box 13)
  - F-802: Traveling exhibits (Box 13)
  - F-803: State/county fairs (Box 13)
  - F-804: Mobile displays (Box 13)
  - F-805: Car shows, general (Box 13)
  - F-806: Hot Rod magazine shows (Box 13)
  - F-807: Foreign shows/exhibits (Box 13)
  - F-808: Show promotion (Box 13)
  - F-809: Collateral material (Box 13)
  - F-900: Sales meetings, general (Box 13)
  - F-901: Sales training (Box 13)
  - F-902: Conventions (Box 14)
  - F-903: Stage shows (Box 14)
  - F-904: Fashion shows (Box 14)
  - F-905: Theatre parties (Box 14)
  - F-906: Hospitality (Box 14)
  - F-907: Invitations (Box 14)
  - F-1000: Presentation methods (Box 14)
  - F-1001: Charts, graphs (Box 14)
  - F-1002: Slides (Box 14)
  - F-1003: Filmstrips (Box 14)
  - F-1004: Film (Box 14)
  - F-1005: Closed circuit, VTR (Box 14)
  - F-1006: Multi-media (Box 14)
  - F-1007: Sales kits (Box 14)
  - F-1100: Motion pictures, general (Box 14)
  - F-1101: Hollywood films (Box 14)
  - F-1102: Motion picture advertising (Box 14)
  - F-1103: Business films (Box 14)
  - F-1104: Business film merchandising (Box 14)
  - F-1200: Advertising specialties, general (Box 14)
  - F-1201: Business gifts (Box 14)
  - F-1202: Sales incentives (Box 14)
  - F-1203: Premiums, general (Box 14)
  - F-1204: Self-liquidating premiums (Box 14)
  - F-1205: Models, toys (Box 14)
  - F-1206: Games, puzzles (Box 14)
  - F-1207: Records, tapes (Box 14)
  - F-1208: Books (Box 14)
  - F-1209: Art (Box 14)
  - F-1300: Inquiry-handling, general (Box 14)
  - F-1301: Response letters (Box 14)
  - F-1302: Forms (Box 14)
  - F-1303: Inquiry-handling services (Box 14)
- G: Publicity/Public Relations, (2 boxes)
  - G-107: News/Feature Services (Box 14)
  - G-1000: Publicity/PR general (Box 14)
  - G-1001: Defining public relations (Box 14)
  - G-1002: Public relations effectiveness (Box 14)
  - G-1003: Historical (Box 14)
  - G-1004: Legal (Box 14)
  - G-1005: Humor (Box 14)
  - G-1006: The PR agency (Box 14)
  - G-1007: Advertising and PR (Box 14)
  - G-1008: The PR director (Box 14)
  - G-1009: Company PR manuals (Box 14)
  - G-1010: Merchandising PR (Box 14)
  - G-2000: Personalities (Box 14)
  - G-2001: PR companies (Box 14)
  - G-2002: Clubs/associations (Box 14)
  - G-2003: Feature services (Box 14)
  - G-2004: Writers/writings (Box 14)
  - G-2005: Methodology/skills (Box 14)
  - G-2006: Releases, general (Box 14)
  - G-2007: New-product releases (Box 14)
  - G-2008: Radio/TV releases (Box 14)
  - G-2009: PR photography (Box 14)
  - G-3000: PR ideas, general (Box 14)
  - G-3001: Career apparel (Box 14)
  - G-3002: Open house, general (Box 14)
  - G-3003: Press receptions (Box 14)
  - G-3004: Backgrounders (Box 14)
  - G-3005: Press kits (Box 14)
  - G-4000: Corporate advertisers (Box 14)
  - G-4001: Multinational PR (Box 14)
  - G-4002: Handling controversy (Box 14)
  - G-4003: Interviews (Box 14)
  - G-4004: Personal PR (Box 14)
  - G-4005: Celebrity PR (Box 14)
  - G-4006: Entertainment PR (Box 14)
  - G-4007: Show/exhibit PR (Box 14)
  - G-4008: Special events, general (Box 14)
  - G-4009: Parades (Box 14)
  - G-4010: Anniversaries (Box 14)
  - G-4011: Bicentennials (Box 14)
  - G-4012: Company histories (Box 15)
  - G-4013: Company museums (Box 15)
  - G-5000: Business-to-business PR (Box 15)
  - G-5001: Financial PR (Box 15)
  - G-5002: Government/military PR (Box 15)
  - G-5003: Customer relations (Box 15)
  - G-5004: Community relations (Box 15)
  - G-5005: Employee relations, general (Box 15)
  - G-5006: Extra-curricular activity (Box 15)
  - G-5007: Communications (Box 15)
  - G-5008: Compensation (Box 15)
  - G-5009: Recruitment (Box 15)
  - G-5010: Morale/loyalty (Box 15)
  - G-5011: Employee representation (Box 15)
  - G-5012: Benefits, general (Box 15)
  - G-5013: Health care (Box 15)
  - G-5014: Emotional counseling (Box 15)
  - G-5015: Workaholism (Box 15)
  - G-5016: Management techniques (Box 15)
  - G-5017: Productivity (Box 15)
  - G-6000: B. Sussman clips (a, b) (Box 15)
  - G-6001: B. Sussman releases (Box 15)
  - G-6002: B. Sussman photos (b, c) (Box 15)
  - G-6003: Old PR shots (Box 15)
- H: Industries, Occupations, (19 boxes)
  - H-100: Industries/occupations, general (Box 15)
  - H-101: For-hire services, general (Box 15)
  - H-102: Prostitution (Box 15)
  - H-103: Personalities, political A-Z (3 folders) (Box 15)
  - H-104: U.S. Presidents (Box 15)
  - H-104: U.S. Presidents (40 folders) (Box 16)
  - H-105: Politics, general (Box 16)
  - H-106: Ralph Nader (Box 16)
  - H-107: Personalities, business (3 folders) (Box 16)
  - H-108: Business, general (Box 16)
  - H-109: Personalities, labor (Box 16)
  - H-110: Labor, general (Box 16)
  - H-111: Personalities, the arts (Box 16)
  - H-112: The arts, general (Box 16)
  - H-113: Personalities, science (Box 16)
  - H-114: Science, general (Box 16)
  - H-115: Personalities, religion (Box 16)
  - H-116: Religion, general (Box 16)
  - H-117: Personalities, education (Box 16)
  - H-118: Education, general (Box 16)
  - H-119: Personalities, mythological (Box 16)
  - H-120: Mythology, general (Box 16)
  - H-121: Personalities, gambling (Box 16)
  - H-122: Gambling, general (Box 16)
  - H-200: Aeronautics, general (Box 16)
  - H-201: Personalities (Box 17)
  - H-202: Historic/developmental (Box 17)
  - H-202a: Aviation history (Box 17)
  - H-203: Restorations (Box 17)
  - H-204: Private aircraft (Box 17)
  - H-205: Helicopters (Box 17)
  - H-206: Lighter-Than-Air (Box 17)
  - H-207: Space program (Box 17)
  - H-208: Foreign, general (Box 17)
  - H-209: Foreign airlines (Box 17)
  - H-210: Domestic airlines, general (Box 17)
  - H-211: Alaskan Airlines (Box 17)
  - H-212: American Airlines (Box 17)
  - H-213: Braniff (Box 17)
  - H-214: Continental (Box 17)
  - H-215: Eastern Airlines (Box 17)
  - H-216: Golden West Airlines (Box 17)
  - H-217: Hawaiian Air, Aloha (Box 17)
  - H-218: National Airlines (Box 17)
  - H-219: Northwest (Box 17)
  - H-220: Pam Am (Box 17)
  - H-221: PSA (Box 17)
  - H-223: Texas International (Box 17)
  - H-224: TWA (Box 17)
  - H-225: Hughes Airwest (Box 17)
  - H-226: United Airlines (Box 17)
  - H-227: Western Airlines (Box 17)
  - H-228: Charter/supplemental (Box 17)
  - H-229: Airfares, general (Box 17)
  - H-230: Civil Aeronautics Board (Box 17)
  - H-231: Aircraft manufacturers (Box 17)
  - H-232: Airports (Box 17)
  - H-234: Safety, control (Box 17)
  - H-235: Psychology, humor (Box 17)
  - H-300: Agriculture, general (Box 17)
  - H-301: Agriculture, government (Box 17)
  - H-302: Livestock (Box 17)
  - H-303: Feed, grain (Box 17)
  - H-304: Equipment (Box 17)
  - H-305: Irrigation/water supply (Box 17)
  - H-306: Psychology/humor (Box 17)
  - H-307: Agriculture, foreign (Box 17)
  - H-400: Antiques, general (Box 17)
  - H-500: Apparel industry, general (Box 17)
  - H-600: Appliances, general (Box 17)
  - H-700: Architecture, general (Box 17)
  - H-701: Architects, designers (Box 17)
  - H-702: Builders (Box 17)
  - H-703: Interiors, modern (Box 18)
  - H-704: Interiors, period (Box 18)
  - H-705: Exteriors, modern (Box 18)
  - H-706: Pre-assembled construction (Box 18)
  - H-706a: Mobile homes (Box 18)
  - H-706b: Mobile home parks (Box 18)
  - H-707: Experimental (Box 18)
  - H-708: Urban renewal (Box 18)
  - H-709: Landscaping (Box 18)
  - H-710: Exteriors, period/historic (Box 18)
  - H-800: Automation, general (Box 18)
  - H-1000: Barbering, general (Box 18)
  - H-1100: Beverages, general (Box 18)
  - H-1101: Distilling (Box 18)
  - H-1102: Retailing (Box 18)
  - H-1103: Liquor recipes (Box 18)
  - H-1104: Beer (Box 18)
  - H-1105: Wine (Box 18)
  - H-1106: Bottling, soft drinks (Box 18)
  - H-1200: Chemical processing (Box 18)
  - H-1300: Cosmetics industry (Box 18)
  - H-1400: Cowboys, Old West, general (Box 18)
  - H-1500: Energy, general (Box 18)
  - H-1501: Shortages, general (Box 18)
  - H-1502: Mid-70s crisis (Box 18)
  - H-1503: Conservation programs (Box 18)
  - H-1504: Carpools (Box 18)
  - H-1505: Speed limits (Box 18)
  - H-1506: Humor (Box 18)
  - H-1507: Legislation (Box 18)
  - H-1510: Petroleum, historical (Box 18)
  - H-1520: OPEC (Box 18)
  - H-1521: Oil/gas exploration (Box 18)
  - H-1522: Oil companies (7 folders) (Box 18)
  - H-1530: Alternate energy sources (Box 19)
  - H-1531: Coal (Box 19)
  - H-1532: Natural gas (Box 19)
  - H-1533: Geothermal energy (Box 19)
  - H-1534: Nuclear energy (Box 19)
  - H-1535: Solar energy (Box 19)
  - H-1536: Hydroelectric power (Box 19)
  - H-1537: Utilities, general (Box 19)
  - H-1600: Environment, general (Box 19)
  - H-1601: Air pollution (Box 19)
  - H-1602: Water pollution (Box 19)
  - H-1603: Trash/solid waste (Box 19)
  - H-1604: Beautification (Box 19)
  - H-1605: Noise pollution (Box 19)
  - H-1606: Environmental control industries (Box 19)
  - H-1700: Financial, general (Box 19)
  - H-1701: Financial media (Box 19)
  - H-1702: Financial advertising (Box 19)
  - H-1703: Financial security (Box 19)
  - H-1704: Financial, humor (Box 19)
  - H-1705: Federal budget (Box 19)
  - H-1706: National economy (Box 19)
  - H-1707: Inflation (Box 19)
  - H-1708: Federal Reserve Board (Box 19)
  - H-1709: Taxes, general (Box 19)
  - H-1710: IMF (Box 19)
  - H-1711: Foreign exchange, general (Box 19)
  - H-1712: Gold market (Box 19)
  - H-1713: Currency printing (Box 19)
  - H-1714: Mints (Box 19)
  - H-1715: Accountants/controllers (Box 19)
  - H-1716: Investment companies (Box 19)
  - H-1717: Mutual funds (Box 19)
  - H-1718: Bonds (Box 19)
  - H-1719: S.E.C. (Box 19)
  - H-1720: N.Y.S.E. (Box 19)
  - H-1721: Pacific Exchange (Box 19)
  - H-1722: Wall Street, general (Box 19)
  - H-1723: Stockbrockers (Box 19)
  - H-1724: Arbitrageurs (Box 19)
  - H-1725: Going public (Box 19)
  - H-1726: 1929+ Depression (Box 19)
  - H-1727: American Express (Box 19)
  - H-1728: Dun & Bradstreet (Box 19)
  - H-1729: Credit, general (Box 19)
  - H-1730: Loans, general (Box 19)
  - H-1731: Credit unions (Box 19)
  - H-1732: Pension systems (Box 19)
  - H-1733: Savings & Loan, general (Box 19)
  - H-1734: National S&L League (Box 19)
  - H-1735: U.S. League of Savings Association (Box 19)
  - H-1736: Premiums (Box 19)
  - H-1737: Individual S&Ls (Box 19)
  - H-1740: Credit cards, general (Box 19)
  - H-1741: American Express (Box 19)
  - H-1742: Carte Blanch (Box 19)
  - H-1743: Diners Club (Box 19)
  - H-1744: Master Charge (Box 19)
  - H-1745: Visa (Box 19)
  - H-1750: Banking, general (Box 19)
  - H-1751: Banking associations (Box 19)
  - H-1752: Systems/equipment (Box 19)
  - H-1753: Bank services (Box 19)
  - H-1754: Prime rates (Box 19)
  - H-1755: Regulations (Box 19)
  - H-1756: Merchant banking (Box 19)
  - H-1757: Individual banks (Box 19)
  - H-1758: Bank of America (Box 19)
  - H-1759: Barclays (Box 19)
  - H-1760: Chase Manhattan (Box 19)
  - H-1761: Crocker National (Box 19)
  - H-1762: Manufacturers Hanover (Box 19)
  - H-1763: Morgan Guaranty (Box 19)
  - H-1764: National City Bank/N.Y. (Box 19)
  - H-1765: Rannier Bank (Box 19)
  - H-1766: UCB (Box 19)
  - H-1767: Union Bank (Box 19)
  - H-1768: Wells Fargo (Box 19)
  - H-1769: Security Pacific (Box 19)
  - H-1775: U.S. banks abroad (Box 19)
  - H-1776: Foreign banks, general (Box 19)
  - H-1777: Rothschilds (Box 19)
  - H-1778: Swiss banking (Box 19)
  - H-1779: British banking (Box 19)
  - H-1780: German banking (Box 19)
  - H-1781: French banking (Box 19)
  - H-1790: International investing (Box 20)
  - H-1800: Fire prevention, general (Box 20)
  - H-1900: Flowers/florists (Box 20)
  - H-2000: Food, general (Box 20)
  - H-2001: Frozen foods, general (Box 20)
  - H-2002: Diet foods (Box 20)
  - H-2003: Dairy products (Box 20)
  - H-2004: Candy (Box 20)
  - H-2005: Fruits/nuts (Box 20)
  - H-2006: Produce (Box 20)
  - H-2008: Catering (Box 20)
  - H-2100: Forestry, general (Box 20)
  - H-2200: Franchising, general (Box 20)
  - H-2400: Furniture, general (Box 20)
  - H-2600: Hardware, general (Box 20)
  - H-2700: Hobbies, general (Box 20)
  - H-2701: Crafts (Box 20)
  - H-2702: Games (Box 20)
  - H-2800: Inventions/patents (Box 20)
  - H-2900: Insurance, general (Box 20)
  - H-3000: Jewelry, general (Box 20)
  - H-3100: Legal, judicial (Box 20)
  - H-3200: Manufacturing, general (Box 20)
  - H-3201: Metalworking (Box 20)
  - H-3203: Materials handling (Box 20)
  - H-3300: Medical, general (Box 20)
  - H-3301: Socialized medicine (Box 20)
  - H-3302: Hospitals, nursing (Box 20)
  - H-3303: Dental (Box 20)
  - H-3304: Optical (Box 20)
  - H-3305: Pharmaceutical (Box 21)
  - H-3306: Veterinary (Box 21)
  - H-3400: Mortuary, cemetary (Box 21)
  - H-3500: Paper products (Box 21)
  - H-3600: Photography, general (Box 21)
  - H-3601: Historical, miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - H-3602: Personalities, general (Box 21)
  - H-3603: Manufacturers, miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - H-3604: Bell & Howell (Box 21)
  - H-3605: Eastman Kodak (Box 21)
  - H-3606: Polaroid (Box 21)
  - H-3607: Photo processes, miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - H-3608: Microfilm (Box 21)
  - H-3609: Advertising photography (Box 21)
  - H-3611: Collecting (Box 21)
  - H-3612: Home movies, miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - H-3613: Photo studios, miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - H-3700: Plastics, general (Box 21)
  - H-3800: Plumbing, general (Box 21)
  - H-3900: Police/law enforcement (Box 21)
  - H-3901: FBI (Box 21)
  - H-3902: Secret Service (Box 21)
  - H-3903: Miscellaneous U.S. police agencies (Box 21)
  - H-3904: Police unions (Box 21)
  - H-3905: California (Box 21)
  - H-3906: New York (Box 21)
  - H-3907: Illinois (Box 21)
  - H-3908: City/state miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - H-3910: Interpol (Box 21)
  - H-3911: Great Britain (Box 21)
  - H-3912: Canada (Box 21)
  - H-3913: France (Box 21)
  - H-3920: Associations (Box 21)
  - H-3921: Police personalities (Box 21)
  - H-3922: Police history (Box 21)
  - H-3923: Police humor (Box 21)
  - H-3924: Fiction/dramatization (Box 21)
  - H-3925: Training/recruitment (Box 21)
  - H-3926: Equipment/weaponry (Box 21)
  - H-3927: Detection techniques (Box 21)
  - H-3928: Intelligence (Box 21)
  - H-3929: Communications (Box 21)
  - H-3930: Transportation (Box 21)
  - H-3935: Crime prevention, general (Box 21)
  - H-3936: Crimes/criminals, general (Box 21)
  - H-3937: Lizzie Borden (Box 21)
  - H-3938: Willie Sutton (Box 21)
  - H-3939: John Wilkes Booth (Box 21)
  - H-3940: Judge Crater (Box 21)
  - H-3941: Daniel Sickles (Box 21)
  - H-3942: Patty Hearst (Box 21)
  - H-3943: Black Dahlia (Box 21)
  - H-3944: Zebra (S.F.) (Box 21)
  - H-3960: Organized crime (Box 21)
  - H-3961: Forgery/counterfeiting (Box 21)
  - H-3962: Bunco (Box 21)
  - H-3963: Computer crime (Box 21)
  - H-3964: Auto theft (Box 21)
  - H-3965: Vandalism (Box 21)
  - H-3966: Narcotics (Box 21)
  - H-3967: Kidnapping (Box 21)
  - H-3968: Skyjacking (Box 21)
  - H-3969: Terrorism (Box 21)
  - H-3970: Subversion (Box 21)
  - H-3971: Riots (Box 21)
  - H-3980: Bail (Box 21)
  - H-3981: Capital punishment (Box 21)
  - H-3982: Punishment, general (Box 21)
  - H-3983: Prisons (Box 21)
  - H-3984: Convicts/ex-convicts (Box 21)
  - H-3985: Security, general (Box 21)
  - H-3986: Private police (Box 21)
  - H-3987: Equipment and manufacturers (Box 21)
  - H-3988: Sentry dogs (Box 21)
  - H-3989: Employee crimes (Box 21)
  - H-3990: Industrial crime (Box 21)
  - H-3991: Shoplifting (Box 21)
  - H-3992: Home security (Box 21)
  - H-4000: Press/publishing, general (Box 21)
  - H-4001: Publishing, historical (Box 21)
  - H-4002: Publishing philosophy (Box 21)
  - H-4003: The reporting process (Box 21)
  - H-4004 (Box 21)
  - H-4005 (Box 21)
  - H-4006: Political cartoons (Box 21)
  - H-4009: Cross-ownership (Box 21)
  - H-4010: Publishers, general (Box 21)
  - H-4011: Publishers, by name
    - ABC Publishing (Box 21)
    - American Express (Box 21)
    - American Heritage (Box 21)
    - Cahners (Box 21)
    - CBS Publishing (Box 21)
    - Chilton (Box 21)
    - Conde-Nast (Box 21)
    - Cowles (Box 21)
    - Crain (Box 21)
    - Crowell (Box 21)
    - Curtis (Box 21)
    - Dun-Donnelly (Box 21)
    - Fairchild (Box 21)
    - Fenton (Box 21)
    - Hearst (Box 21)
    - Maclean-Hunter (Box 22)
    - McGraw-Hill (Box 22)
    - Murdoch (Box 22)
    - Newhouse (Box 22)
    - Peterson (Box 22)
    - Playboy (Box 22)
    - Time-Life (Box 22)
    - Ziff-Davis (Box 22)
  - H-4012: Foreign-language press (Box 22)
  - H-4013: Foreign publishing, general (Box 22)
  - H-4014: Supplements (Box 22)
  - H-4015: Almanacs (Box 22)
  - H-4016: Comics (Box 22)
  - H-4017: Technology (Box 22)
  - H-4018: Subscriptions, general (Box 22)
  - H-4021: Publishing/literary personalities (Box 22)
  - H-4022-H-4029: Personalitites A-Z (Box 22)
  - H-4040: Magazines, general (Box 22)
  - H-4041: Foreign magazines (Box 22)
  - H-4042: Esquire (Box 22)
  - H-4043: Forbes (Box 22)
  - H-4044: Harper's (Box 22)
  - H-4045: Ladies Home Journal (Box 22)
  - H-4046: Liberty (Box 22)
  - H-4047: Life (Box 22)
  - H-4048: Look (Box 22)
  - H-4049: McCall's (Box 22)
  - H-4050: Newsweek (Box 22)
  - H-4051: New West (Box 22)
  - H-4052: New Yorker (Box 22)
  - H-4053: Penthouse/Viva (Box 22)
  - H-4054: Quest (Box 22)
  - H-4055: Reader's Digest (Box 22)
  - H-4056: Rolling Stone (Box 22)
  - H-4057: Saturday Evening Post (Box 22)
  - H-4058: Saturday Review (Box 22)
  - H-4059: Sunset (Box 22)
  - H-4060: Town and Country (Box 22)
  - H-4061: TV Guide (Box 22)
  - H-4062: Trades, general (Box 22)
  - H-4063: MAC, etc. (Box 22)
  - H-4064: Inland Printer (Box 22)
  - H-4070: Newspapers, general (Box 22)
  - H-4071: Labor relations (Box 22)
  - H-4072: Groups/chains (Box 22)
  - H-4073: Foreign newspapers (Box 22)
  - H-4074: Financial press (Box 22)
  - H-4075: Military press (Box 22)
  - H-4076: National newspapers (Box 22)
  - H-4077: California newspapers (Box 22)
  - H-4078: L.A. area newspapers (Box 22)
  - H-4079: L.A. Daily News (Box 22)
  - H-4080: L.A. Herald-Examiner (Box 22)
  - H-4081: L.A. Times (Box 22)
  - H-4082: New York newspapers (Box 22)
  - H-4083: Chicago newspapers (Box 22)
  - H-4084: St. Louis newspapers (Box 22)
  - H-4085: Washington, D.C. newspapers (Box 22)
  - H-4086: City newspapers, miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - H-4090: Creative/production (Box 22)
  - H-4091: Marketing/advertising (Box 22)
  - H-4092: Advertiser merchandising (Box 22)
  - H-4093: Editorial merchandising (Box 22)
  - H-4094: Distribution, general (Box 22)
  - H-4095: Mail/postage (Box 22)
  - H-4096: Newsstands (Box 22)
  - H-4100: Real estate, general (Box 22)
  - H-4100: Ethics/credibility (Box 22)
  - H-4101: Legal, general (Box 22)
  - H-4102: Censorship/controversy (Box 22)
  - H-4103: Censorship, historical (Box 22)
  - H-4104: Anthony Comstock (Box 22)
  - H-4105: Pin-ups (Box 22)
  - H-4106: Obscenity/pornography (Box 22)
  - H-4107: Violence (Box 22)
  - H-4108: Press freedom, general (Box 22)
  - H-4109: Editorial leaks (Box 22)
  - H-4110: Confidential sources (Box 22)
  - H-4111: Pre-trial publicity (Box 22)
  - H-4120: Books, general (Box 22)
  - H-4121: Books, historical (Box 22)
  - H-4122: Rare/original editions (Box 22)
  - H-4123: Book publishing (Box 22)
  - H-4124: Book production (Box 22)
  - H-4125: Book publishers (Box 22)
  - H-4126: Marketing, general (Box 22)
  - H-4127: Book retailing (Box 22)
  - H-4128: Book clubs (Box 22)
  - H-4129: Best seller lists (Box 22)
  - H-4130: Libraries (Box 22)
  - H-4131: Fiction, general (Box 22)
  - H-4132: Non-fiction, general (Box 22)
  - H-4133: Textbooks (Box 22)
  - H-4134: Directories (Box 22)
  - H-4135: Encyclopedias (Box 22)
  - H-4136: Paperbacks, general (Box 22)
  - H-4140: Greeting cards, general (Box 22)
  - H-4141: Greeting cards, historical (Box 22)
  - H-4142: Hallmark Cards, Inc. (Box 22)
  - H-4143: Greeting card publishers (Box 22)
  - H-4200: Retailing, general (Box 22)
  - H-4300: Restaurants/Taverns (Box 23)
  - H-4301: Associations, general (Box 23)
  - H-4302: Southern California Restaurant Association (Box 23)
  - H-4303: Historic (Box 23)
  - H-4304: Humor (Box 23)
  - H-4305: Personalities (Box 23)
  - H-4306: Decor (Box 23)
  - H-4307: In-plant feeding (Box 23)
  - H-4308: Institutions, general (Box 23)
  - H-4309: North American, general (Box 23)
  - H-4310: Southern California, general (Box 23)
  - H-4311: Foreign, general (Box 23)
  - H-4312: Health food (Box 23)
  - H-4313: Taverns/saloons (Box 23)
  - H-4314: Drive-ins, general (Box 23)
  - H-4315: Bob's Big Boy (Box 23)
  - H-4316: Fred Harvey (Box 23)
  - H-4317: Horn and Hardart (Box 23)
  - H-4318: Love's (Box 23)
  - H-4319: Victoria Station (Box 23)
  - H-4320: Hamburger Hamlet (Box 23)
  - H-4321: Musso and Frank (Box 23)
  - H-4322: Trader Vic (Box 23)
  - H-4323: Fast foods, general (Box 23)
  - H-4324: Fast foods, foreign (Box 23)
  - H-4325: A&W (Box 23)
  - H-4326: Burger Chef (Box 23)
  - H-4327: Burger King (Box 23)
  - H-4328: Carl's Jr. (Box 23)
  - H-4329: Colonel Sanders (Box 23)
  - H-4330: Denny's (Box 23)
  - H-4331: Der Wienerschnitzel (Box 23)
  - H-4332: Host International (Box 23)
  - H-4333: Howard Johnson (Box 23)
  - H-4334: International House of Pancakes (Box 23)
  - H-4335: Jack-in-the-Box (Box 23)
  - H-4336: Lums (Box 23)
  - H-4337: McDonald's (Box 23)
  - H-4338: Orange Julius (Box 23)
  - H-4339: Pizza Hut (Box 23)
  - H-4340: Sambo's (Box 23)
  - H-4341: Shakey's (Box 23)
  - H-4342: Taco Bell (Box 23)
  - H-4400: Scouting, general (Box 23)
  - H-4500: Sporting goods, general (Box 23)
  - H-4600: Sports/athletics, general (Box 23)
  - H-4600a: Olympics (Box 23)
  - H-4601: Archery (Box 23)
  - H-4602: Badminton (Box 23)
  - H-4603: Baseball (Box 23)
  - H-4604: Basketball (Box 23)
  - H-4605: Bicycling (Box 23)
  - H-4611: Bowling (Box 23)
  - H-4612: Boxing (Box 23)
  - H-4613: Bullfighting (Box 23)
  - H-4614: Calisthenics (Box 23)
  - H-4615: Camping (Box 23)
  - H-4616: Fencing (Box 23)
  - H-4617: Fishing (Box 23)
  - H-4618: Football (Box 23)
  - H-4619: Golf (Box 23)
  - H-4620: Hockey (Box 23)
  - H-4621: Horse racing (Box 24)
  - H-4622: Hunting, guns (Box 24)
  - H-4623: Lacrosse (Box 24)
  - H-4624: Mountain climbing (Box 24)
  - H-4625: Parachuting (Box 24)
  - H-4626: Polo (Box 24)
  - H-4627: Rodeo (Box 24)
  - H-4628: Skating (Box 24)
  - H-4629: Skin diving (Box 24)
  - H-4630: Skiing (Box 24)
  - H-4631: Soccer/rugby (Box 24)
  - H-4632: Surfing (Box 24)
  - H-4633: Swimming (Box 24)
  - H-4634: Tobagganing (Box 24)
  - H-4635: Tennis (Box 24)
  - H-4636: Track (Box 24)
  - H-4637: Water polo (Box 24)
  - H-4638: Weight lifting (Box 24)
  - H-4639: Wrestling (Box 24)